<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on PRN ?</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on PRN ?</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 06:06:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Nursing Teams : Acute care vs Critical care</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/surgvsicu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 06:06:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/surgvsicu/</guid>
      <description>[]&#xA;You ever worked in that hospital , on that unit where you’re running around and you look around and the other nurses were just sitting , browsing….&#xA;Up until 2 years ago I worked in acute care, I’ve worked in a few of these units , and in I feel like most of nights went like above. I should also mention that I primarily work nights. I would sit and watch the routine of these MedSurg/ Tele nurses, the mad rush to finish your tasks and then “have a good night “, and complain if you had a patient(s) disrupt this routine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caringvsconvenience</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/caringvsconvenience/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 06:51:52 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/caringvsconvenience/</guid>
      <description>Nursing has obviously evolved into the technologically advanced, almost cure-all profession we know today.&#xA;If it were possible to pull back the blinds and see what our founders&amp;rsquo; intentions were, how they practiced then, and how they practiced five decades ago.&#xA;As I referenced yesterday, chemical and physical solutions are sometimes necessary. However, the healthcare field has instituted changes in the last couple of decades that I&amp;rsquo;ve been practicing to understand that these measures aren&amp;rsquo;t always necessary and can lead to negative outcomes at times.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Art of calm</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/artofcalm/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 08:15:44 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/artofcalm/</guid>
      <description>Fundamentally, nursing is about caring, right?&#xA;How caring are you still after a long string of rude patients cursing you out, or another CIWA patient trying to hit you, or that cute elderly patient slapping you?&#xA;With all the stressors of life, let alone the ones in the nursing field, weighing heavily on nurses, it&amp;rsquo;s understandable to get upset in these situations.&#xA;I truly believe that the way a nurse reacts sets the tone for the shift, the entire hospital stay, and maybe even the rest of the patients&amp;rsquo; and nurses&amp;rsquo; lives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intro</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 12:44:38 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>Heading level 3 !Disclaimer! These are just my personal views, opinions, and rants about the nursing field. I&amp;rsquo;m definitely no expert writer and even with the two decades of experience in the field, I do not make any claims to be the foremost expert in this field . What I&amp;rsquo;m hoping for is funny but respectful comments, constructive criticism and any valuable input. I&amp;rsquo;m hoping to grow , become better by interacting with my peers on this forum.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
